http://www.falon-nameplates.co.uk/privacy-policy/

HomeOur ProductsMemorial PlaquesLand RoverHouse PlatesGrave MarkersSignage/TourisimHeritage & War MemorialsEngineering PlatesTrophies & EngravingsShop OnlineAbout UsTestimonialsClaireMr HarrisonMrs WhiteMr WickensLuigiCarolMichaelEmilyStephenMrs JamesMr ReidGood ConditionGood Condition (1)GoodGood (1)lrGood CommentslandyLandy (1)Mr RoweGet a QuoteBlogContactFAQ
My Basket (0)
01670 530136
Log in
Register an Account
HomeOur ProductsMemorial PlaquesLand RoverHouse PlatesGrave MarkersSignage/TourisimHeritage & War MemorialsEngineering PlatesTrophies & EngravingsShop OnlineAbout UsTestimonialsGet a QuoteBlogContactFAQ
HomePrivacy Policy
Copyright © Falon Nameplates, all rights reserved. Unless otherwise stated, the copyright of all the information, materials, images, logos, downloadable documents and video content on this website belongs to Falon Nameplates. Information may not be published in any other format without express written permission.
Privacy policy Falon Nameplates is committed to protecting the personal information of all visitors to this website.
In order to carry out work on your behalf we collect the following personally identifying information when you submit an enquiry form;
Full Name
Email address
Telephone
Data Usage
This Data is required in order that we may communicate with you and/or your business to aid us with carrying out services as contracted by you.
Sharing Your Data
We only share information where required by law or with carefully selected contractors and specialists to help us provide our services. We only share Data with other companies who are GDPR or ISO 27001 compliant. We are careful to minimise such sharing.
We may also share your personal Data if:
The Law or a public authority says we must share that Data
If we need to share personal Data in order to establish or defend our legal rights, this includes providing personal Data to others for the purposes of preventing fraud and reducing credit risk o any other successors in title to our business
Your Rights and Choices
You have the right to see the personal Data we hold about you under the GDPR, this is called a Subject Access Request. If you wish to see this Data then please inform us in writing or via our contact form.
Please inform us if you believe any of the Data we hold regarding you is inaccurate and we will update accordingly.
You also have the right to ask us to delete all personal Data we hold about you. Again, please submit this request via email.
Google Analytics/Cookies
In order to improve your experience on our site, we may use cookies. Cookies are small files that are widely used in order to make websites work more efficiently. Most web browsers allow some control of cookies through browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage or delete them from your computer, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
We may, from time to time, engage in re-marketing, which means third-party vendors, including Google, may display our adverts on the internet, based on your prior interaction with our website. To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Any information collected via cookies is used solely for this purpose and no other purpose.
Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google and we use our reports provided by Google Analytics in order to help understand our traffic and usage of the website.
Falon Nameplates Limited
10-13 Stephenson Court, Barrington Industrial Estate,
Follow Us:
Molded and Forged by:
Retox Digital
Back to top
